警察学校
警察学校:
莫斯科
进军
准备 开拍 5 4 3 2…
And ready, here we go. Five, four, three, two
晚上好 台湾惨案
Good evening. Tragedy in Taiwan.
丹麦天灾 马来人祸
Disaster in Denmark. Mayhem in Malaysia.
稍后将向您进行详细报道
Those stories and more coming up later.
今晚话题：声称为俄国黑手党领袖的康斯坦丁·康那利…
the computer game phenomenon...
…发布的电子游戏如暴风雨般席卷整个世界
...distributed by alleged Russian Mafia leader Konstantine Konali...
…天寒地冻的俄罗斯…
...has taken the world by storm. Out of the cold climates of Russia...
…制造了一股火热的游戏浪潮…
...comes the hottest computer game sensation...
…游戏的名字非常简单 叫做…"游戏"埃得?
...simply called ''The Game. '' Ed?
- 埃得 你在干嘛? - 你也应该玩玩这个游戏 它棒极了
- Ed, what are you doing? - You gotta try this game. lt's great.
现在不成 埃得在过去的六个月里…
Not now, Ed. ln the past six months...
"游戏"使得国家税收增加了15亿美元
... ''The Game'' has generated over $ 1 .5 billion in revenue...
- …打破了以往的任何纪录 - 抓住他! 你这个可怜的小熊!
- ...breaking all previous records. - Get him, you miserable bear!
是什么使得这项游戏如此与众不同? 这是首次电子游戏…
What makes this game stand out? This is the first time that a video game...
…同时占据了少年… - 埃得!
...has appealed to a youthful... - Ed!
…与成年人的市场
...as well as a more sophisticated market.
- 噢 嘘 - "游戏"不仅有游戏卡…
- Oh, sh    - ''The Game,'' available in cartridges...
也有电脑磁盘每个人都在玩它
...as well as floppy disks for computer, has everybody playing.
把它抢过来 林德茜 抢过来!
Take it, Lindsay, take it.
"游戏"的发明者及发行者都是康斯坦丁·康那利…
The creator and mass - marketer of ''The Game'' is Konstantine Konali...
- …俄国黑手党的领袖 - 不 不 不!
- ...allegedly head of the Russian Mafia. - No, no, no!
康那利和…他在莫斯科干什么?
Konali and   What is he up to in Moscow?
别再玩了!
Get your hands off it.
- 把你的手拿开! - 把它给我!
- Get your hands off the game! - l want that game!
我才不会把我的东西给你! 把它给我!
l'm not giving you my game! Give it to me!
- 你在这家电视台玩完了 - 你才玩蛋了呢!
You're through at this station. You're through.
米沙 好好照顾我的小日本妞儿
Misha, take care of Skippy.
哎…
Ay.
狮子流星啊狮子流星…
Leonid, Leonid, Leonid.
已经受够了黑暗下的生活
Enough living in the shadows.
总有一天…
Someday...
…这一切将…
...this will all...
…都是我的!
...be mine!
- 犯罪问题已经无法控制 - 是的 鲍里斯·尼古拉耶维奇
MAN 1 : This crime problem is out of hand. MAN 2: Yes, Boris Nikolayevich.
我们需要帮助
We need help.
我推荐一个我在国际会议上认识的一个人
I can recommend a man I met during the international conference.
我听说他在康那利还在美国的时候…
I understand he has already had dealings with Konali...
…就和他有过接触
... when Konali was in America.
我会把这调查清楚
l will make this very clear.
他能帮我们抓到康那利吗?
Can he help us get Konali?
是的 鲍里斯·尼古拉耶维奇他正是这项工作的恰当人选
Yes, Boris Nikolayevich. He is just the man for the job.
随时向我报告
Keep me informed.
啊
Ah.
噢
Oh.
过去啰 孩子
There you are, son.
新学员们做的怎么样?
How are the new recruits doing?
这是有史以来最棒的一个班 但除了一个人
lt might be the best class ever, except for one man.
- 他有恐高症 - 看看你能为他做什么
- He's afraid of heights. - See what you can do for him.
有时最糟糕的学员会成长为最棒的军官
l find that sometimes the least likely cadets make the finest police officers.
拉萨校长 请把球扔给我们!
Commandant Lassard, throw us the ball.
打到记分牌上…
Off the scoreboard...
…再经地板 撞到墙上…
...off the floor, off the wall...
…打到红发小妞的头上…
...off the redhead.
完美无瑕
Nothing but net.
- 不错 - 我爱这项运动
- Not bad. - l love this game.
康那斯? 康那斯在哪?
Connors. Where's Connors?
谢谢 康那斯 你把它修好了
Thanks, Connors. You fixed it.
这是警察机密文件
That's a classified police file.
"学校组织了一个小队去莫斯科执行特殊任务"
''The academy has assembled a special team for a mission to Moscow. ''
我会为这个任务疯狂的
l'd kill for that job.
名单上有韦伯斯特 为什么是他?
Webster's on the list. Why him?
可能因为我们班上他最先毕业
Because he graduated first in our class.
嗯 好…
Yeah, well...
…他能这样吗?
...can he do this?
能
Yep.
这个呢?
Can he do this?
- 能 - 我也就会这些了
- Yep. - That's all l got.
你这是干什么?
What are you doing?
- 噢 我从没有去过俄罗斯 - 行了 现在把它改回去
- Well, l've never been to Russia. - Okay, now put it back.
康那斯 中士要见你
Connors. Sergeant wants you.
- 是的 - 现在
- Yeah. MAN: Now.
见到你们我真是太太太高兴了
l'm so very, very glad to see you.
莫斯科警方请求我们携助他们…
The Moscow police have asked us to assist them...
- …抓捕康斯坦丁·康那利 - 俄国佬?
- ...in apprehending Konstantine Konali. MAN: Russkies?
俄国的教父在组织犯罪活动
The godfather of Russian organized crime.
啊…
Men... .
6年前…
Six years ago...
…康那利帮助俄国黑手党在我们这…
...Konali helped to establish a branch of the Russian Mafia here...
…在我们国家里成立了分支
...in our country.
那时候就差点抓到他
Nearly got him then.
不幸的是 他从我们的指缝间遛走 逃回了莫斯科…
Unfortunately, he slipped through our fingers and escaped back to Moscow...
…并继续从事他的犯罪活动…
... where he continues his criminal activities...
…同时得到了他兄弟米克黑尔和他的宠物蛇小日本妞的帮助
...aided by his brother Mikhail and pet snake Skippy.
本垒打!
Home run!
现在我们又有机会抓住他了
Now we get another chance to apprehend him.
噢 真是个笨蛋!
Man, what a wimp.
康那斯 下来! 你永远也过不了考试
Connors, get down here. You're never gonna pass the test.
我一定要过! 我爸爸曾经就是警察!
l've gotta pass. My father was a cop.
他的爸爸也是个警察嗯 他的爸爸是个盗马贼
His father was a cop. His father was a horse thief.
- 你已经晕菜了 快下来! - 晕菜? 哈!
- You got vertigo. Let's go. - Vertigo. Ha!
我才没有
l don't have vertigo.
唷 康那斯 想来个甜甜圈吗?
Yo, Connors, you want a doughnut?
- 不错 - 康那斯 我们应该面对现实
Not bad. Connors, let's face it.
要做警察你还不够格
You don't have what it takes to be a cop.
拿着这个去拉萨校长的办公室
Take this to Commandant Lassard's office.
- 他会在你的开除学籍证明上签字 - 娇生惯养的公子哥儿
- He'll sign off on your dismissal papers. CADET 4: Bummer, dude.
现在 我想让你见一下…
Now, l want you to meet...
…我们队里的新成员
...a new addition to our team.
- 你一定就是学员康那斯 - 嗨
- You must be Cadet Connors. - Hi.
你的资料给我留下了非常非常深刻的印象
l'm very, very impressed by your file.
- 凯尔·康那斯学员 - 嗯
- Cadet Kyle Connors. - Mm.
班级里平均分数最高的学员
Top grade average in the class.
长官 我得跟您说件事情
Sir, I have to tell you something.
祝贺你
Congratulations.
谢谢 但我真的不是文件里说的那个人
Thanks, but l'm not really the man in that file.
噢 我懂你的意思
Oh, l know what you mean.
这些报告从来无法反映真实的我们
These reports never do give an accurate picture of who we really are.
- 啊? - 是的 但是
- Hm? - Yes, but
啊噢!
Ow!
噢!
Ooh!
这到底是什么玩意儿?
What the hell is this?
啊哈
Uh - huh.
快 快 快!
Come on, come on. Come on.
- 我们一起 - 好的
- Let's all pull together. WOMAN: Okay.
好了 我数到三 大伙一起拉! 一 二 三!
Okay, all together, on three! One, two, three!
- 噢 上帝! - 长官!
Oh, God. - Sir!
啊! 哈里斯上尉! 我们的密探 也来加入我们了!
Ah! Captain Harris, our expert in surveillance, will be accompanying us.
队员们 我们一起进军莫斯科…
Team, we're all off to Russia...
…去踢许多许多的俄国佬的屁股!
...to kick many, many butt - skis.
啊 亚力山大·尼古拉维奇
Ah, Alexander Nikolaivitch.
伙计们…
Men...
…这就是伟大的亚力山大·尼古拉维奇·拉科夫指挥官
...this is the honorable Commandant Alexander Nikolaivitch Rakov.
- （俄语）你好 - 我能不能这样说：伟大的拉萨指挥官的来访…
- Sasha. - May l say it is an honor...
…真是我们国家的荣耀
...to have the great Commandant Lassard visiting our country?
- 是的 你能 - 我能再亲您一次吗?
- Yes, you may. - May l kiss you again?
- 不 不能 - 我能护送您进去吗?
- No, you may not. - May l escort you inside?
是的 你能
Yes, you may.
您能来俄罗斯真是太棒了!
lt is really wonderful to have you here in Russia.
请代我向您夫人问好…
Please say hello to your lovely wife...
…并转达我对她未能前来的遗憾
...and tell her l'm sorry she's not here with you.
噢 对了 尤里·塔林斯基中尉
Yes. Lieutenant Yuri Talinsky.
我们的有组织犯罪侦察科的领导
Head of our organized crime unit.
不要低估俄国黑手党的力量…
Please, don't underestimate the power of the Russian Mafia...
…他们是世界上最邪恶的组织
...the most sadistic organization in the world.
卡特娅
Katya.
这是卡特娅·赛尔盖中士
This is Sergeant Katya Sergei.
她被选中作您们的导游与翻译
She has been handpicked to be your guide and translator.
塔林斯基中尉 我授权你负责…
Lieutenant Talinsky, l hold you personally responsible...
…拉萨指挥官及其一行人的舒适与安全问题
...for the comfort and safety of the Americans and Commandant Lassard.
- 是 长官 - 现在 美俄联手…
- Yes, sir. - Now, Americans and Russians...
…我们一起抓住这个毒虫康那利…
...we must grab Konali like the insect that he is...
…然后踩死他!
...and we must then crush him!
- 上帝 - 让开 让开 琼斯
- God. HARRlS: Make way. Jones. Jones.
- 琼斯 让道 让道! - 噢!
- Jones. Make way. Make way. - Oh!
我是赛德伊斯·哈里斯上尉 在这个箱子里…
l am Captain Thaddeus Harris and in this case...
…有我们美国技术一流的监视装备
...l have state - of - the - art American surveillance equipment.
我会为您在几天之内将康那利的事情解决掉
l'll have this Konali business wrapped up for you in a few days.
对不起 里基我必须去趟洗手间
Excuse me, Ricky. l must go to the toilet.
当然 您请
Yes, of course.
- 对不起 哪辆车是我的? - 前面那辆
- Pardon me. Which is my car? - The one in front.
前面的…噢 是了
The one in front. Oh, yeah.
（俄语）
- 他说什么? - 嗯 他说您的态度非常虔诚…
- What did he say? - Well, he said that you had...
…跟您一起共事真是愉快 长官
...a marvelous attitude and you're a pleasure to work with, sir.
我会一直盯着你的
l'm going to keep my eye on you.
红色区域为共产党员专用车位
The red zone is for Communist parking only.
前面的那辆…
The one in front.
红色区域为共产党员专用车位
The red zone is for Communist parking only.
噢 您好
Oh, hello.
塔林斯基没告诉我他的家人也来了
Lieutenant Talinsky didn't tell me his family would be here.
你们能来接我真是太好了
Very nice of you to come and greet me.
卡特琳娜 我想让你把我当成友好的美国使馆大使
Katrina, l want you to think of me as America's goodwill ambassador.
你把我当成翻译和导游就成了
And you think of me as translator and guide.
停下! 停下!
Stop! Stop!
唉! 唉呀呀呀呀!
Ay! Ay - yai - yai - yai - yai.
我惨了…
l'm in deep borscht.
（俄语）
卡拉汉上尉 511房琼斯中士 513
Captain Callahan, 51 1 . Sergeant Jones, 51 3.
塔克贝利中士 514康那斯学员 520
Sergeant Tackleberry, 51 4. Cadet Connors, 520.
哈里斯上尉 515
Captain Harris, 51 5.
这不是真正的四星级酒店吧 啊?
Not exactly a four - star hotel, is it?
我们的经费都用在与犯罪分子作斗争上…
Well, we spend our police budget on fighting criminals...
…而不是用在外地旅游者身上
...not on pampering out - of - town visitors.
是你们的政府带我们来的
Your government brought us here.
他们也为动物园带来猴子…
They also bring in monkeys for zoo...
…我们也不会把它们送进四星级酒店
...but we don't put them in four - star hotel either.
嗯 我现在去看看拉萨指挥官
Well, l just go check on Commandant Lassard.
拉萨 拉萨 你!
Lassard. Lassard. You!
你
You.
- 嗯哼 - 你
- Hm - mm. - You.
我给你找了个活干
l have job for you.
再说一遍：当你听见敲门时 你就说：
Again. When you hear door, you say:
"我在洗澡 我一会儿去找你"
''l'm in the bathroom. l'll meet you there. ''
"我在洗澡 在那等我"
''l'm in the bathroom. Meet me there. ''
再来一遍
Again.
"我在洗澡 我一会儿去找你"
''l'm in the bathroom. l'll meet you there. ''
"我在洗澡 一会儿去找你"
''l'm in the bathroom. Meet you there. ''
请进
Come in.
再来一遍!
Again!
"我在洗澡 在那等我"
''ln the bathroom. Meet me there. ''
对不起 指挥官在吗?
Excuse me. ls the commandant in?
噢 我刚见过他 他非常累 想休息一会儿
Well, l just saw him. He's very tired and enjoying moment of rest.
啊 谢谢
Ah. Thank you.
（俄语）
我得过关 哦…
l have to get to next level. Eh... .
- 在找什么吗 上尉? - 虫子 你不能不细心
- Looking for something, captain? - Bugs. You can never be too careful.
- 因为我小心谨慎 - 你是多疑症
- Call me paranoid. - You're paranoid.
我只剩一条命了 我老过不去
l'm down to one life. l can't make it.
我能教您点小技巧吗?
Can l show you a little trick?
看着 你就想让小熊往后走三步 是吗?
Watch. You just want the bear to go back three spaces. Right?
瞧见了?
See?
啊 它过关了
lt makes it to next level.
- 我过关了 谢谢 - 游戏
- l made it. Thank you. - Game.
早上好
Good morning, everyone.
我了解到你们的指挥官今天不能出席
l understand that your commandant will not be joining us today.
不管怎样 我们还是继续我们的情况介绍
However, we will proceed with briefing anyway.
康斯坦丁·康那利 俄国黑手党的教父
Konstantine Konali, Russian Mafia godfather.
琼斯!
Jones!
他的兄弟 也就是二头目 米克黑尔·康那利
His brother and second - in - command, Mikhail Konali.
康斯坦丁·康那利涉嫌敲诈勒索…
Konstantine Konali is involved in extortion...
…赌博 买卖脏物及军火交易
...gambling, fencing jewelry, arms dealing.
但他自己却从不卷入…
But he does not choose to involve himself...
- 卷心菜吃多了 - …每天的犯罪活动
JONES: Too much cabbage. - ...in day - to - day running of operations...
…这让我们很难抓住他 尽管如此…
...which makes it rather difficult to catch him. However...
…我们知道他经常出没的三个地点…
...we know three places that he frequents regularly.
一 他的酒店…
his restaurant...
…他经常在后面办公室里开会
...where he conducts meetings in back of office.
二 他的别墅三…
his dacha.
喂 喂
Hello. Hello.
他的商店 他在那里经营合法的游戏生意现在…
His warehouse, where he conducts legitimate video games business. Now...
…我们有理由相信康那利在进行着大的阴谋活动
...we believe Konali is up to something big.
不幸的是 我们曾试图诱使他行动但没有成功…
Unfortunately, attempts to infiltrate his operations have failed...
…但现在我们一起共事 我们一定会抓住康那利的!
...but we will now work together and we will capture Konali.
康那利的酒店
- 打扰一下 - 啊喔!
- Excuse me. MALE VOlCE: Ow!
亚当
Adam.
见到你真高兴
So good to see you.
谢谢您邀请我 康那利先生不过您的快递服务…
Thank you for inviting me, Mr. Konali. However, your delivery service...
…还有待改善
...leaves a little bit to be desired.
我有一个完美的计划 需要你的帮助
l have the perfect plan, but l need your help.
- 我的帮助? - 我要你设计一个程序…
- My help? - l want you to design a program...
…一个可以让我通过世界上任何一台电脑的安全系统…
...that will bypass any computer security system in the world...
…并得到秘密文件的程序
...letting me have access to secret files.
您指的是…
You're talking about...
- …一把密码钥匙? - 对了!
- ...a passkey? - Bingo.
- 世上不存在这种东西 - 那就创造它
- Nothing like this exists. - Create it.
我要进入世界银行系统…
l want to be able to tap into the world's banks...
…操纵全世界的股市还要知道国家的头儿们都知道什么
...manipulate the world's stock markets, know what heads of countries know.
我们要控制全世界!
We could control the world!
再大点声 啊? 我觉得整个莫斯科听不到你的声音
Louder, Misha. l don't think all of Moscow heard you.
即使我真的创造了这个程序 你又如何用它进入他们的电脑呢?
Even if l did create this passkey, how will you get it into their computers?
我早就想过了
l have already thought of that.
你 我亲爱的亚当 要开发新版本的"游戏"
You, my dear Adam, will design a new version of ''The Game. ''
我们就给它起名叫…
We will call it...
…"新游戏"
... ''The New Game. ''
然后在其中加上这个程序
And we will put the passkey in it.
当你把它插入你的电脑后巴达叮!
When you slip it into your computer, bada - bing!
我就能得到那些秘密文件了不错吧?
l will have access to impenetrable files. Pretty good, no?
拉萨
Lassard.
呸! 美国条子!
Bah! Yankee police.
噢喔!
Ow!
伙计们 盯着他们
Boys, watch them.
我要知道他们的每一步行动
l want to know their every move.
好运 （俄语）老女人
Good luck, babushka.
哦
Uh... .
在洗澡 一会儿见在洗
''ln the bathroom. Meet you there. ln the
在洗澡 是的
ln the bathroom. '' Yes.
长官 我们得走了
Sir, we have to go now.
- 长官? - 在洗澡!
- Sir? - ln the bathroom.
- 一会见 - 出什么事了吗?
- Meet you there. - ls everything okay?
长官正在解决一些个人问题
The commandant is having some problems adjusting.
- 他一会去找我们 - 哼
- He's gonna meet us there. - Oh.
呼!
Whew!
你知道 在美国葬礼是用英语的
You know, in America, funerals are in English.
您住在这儿?
This where you live?
您好
Good day.
- （俄语）这个怪老头儿是谁? - 我不知道
我也有一条鱼
l have a fish.
他也住在一个缸里
He lives in a bowl too.
您的公寓真是非常非常可爱
You have a lovely, lovely apartment.
我在这感觉就像家一样
Somehow, l feel quite at home here.
俄国佬的警察学校? 真可笑
A Russki police academy. What a joke.
莫斯科警察学校
在拉萨不在的时候 我来作发言人
ln Lassard's absence, l will do all the talking.
你们什么都不许说 也不许做注意你们的行动
You'll say nothing, do nothing, watch your every move.
都给我老实点儿任何错误的行动都会让我们所有人丢尽颜面
Be on your toes. Any false move could embarrass us all.
不要相信这群人
And don't trust these guys.
不要因为我们现在是合作关系…
Just because we're buddy - buddy with them now...
…就忘记了我们曾是不共戴天的敌人
...don't forget they were our sworn enemies just
一小会儿之前
Just a little while ago.
- 让开 让开 让开! - 白痴
- Move it. Move it, move it. MAN: Moron.
今天的话题是警察战术
The topic for today is police field tactics.
俄国与美国警察工作方法比较
The Russian and the American approach.
啊 一个美国警察 很好
American police. Good.
也许你能向我们讲述一下如何抓捕罪犯
Perhaps you can tell us about apprehending criminals.
- 我? - 你 就是你
- Me? - You. You.
看在上帝的份儿上
Goodness' sakes.
- 少校 - 中士
- Major. - Sergeant.
同学们 这是塔克贝利中士
Class, this is Sergeant Tackleberry.
嗯 你们知道 作为警察
Okay. You know, as cops
我用不着告诉你们这些
l don't have to tell you this.
维护法律不是容易的事情而且在美国…
lt's tough to uphold the law, but in the States...
…我们必须应对不断变化的警察规则
...we have to deal with constantly changing police regulations.
我的意思是 例如滥用暴力
l mean, take for example the excessive force issue.
- 我需要一个志愿者 - 塔克贝利 你在干什么?
- l could use a volunteer. - Tackleberry, what are you doing?
这里我负责
l am in charge here.
哈里斯上尉 也许你该来做个示范
Captain Harris, perhaps you should demonstrate.
- 哼 这才像话 - 在以前…
- Well, that's more like it. - Back in the old days...
…为了抓住嫌疑犯没有什么你不能做的
...there wasn't anything you couldn't do trying to apprehend a perpetrator.
比如最有效的扼住喉咙
Take for example the highly effective chokehold.
塔克贝利!
Tackleberry!
现在这被认作滥用暴力
Well, nowadays this is considered to be excessive force.
或者…
Or...
…一直最值得信赖 最有效的PK - 24警棍…
...the ever - dependable, always reliable PK - 24 police baton...
…只要往身上敲一下…
...which, with a single blow to the body...
…击打下肢…
...say to the lower thigh... .
…致使对方完全丧失行为能力
Renders a subject completely incapacitated.
不 噢 不
But, no, no.
现在这两样都被视力滥用暴力
Nowadays this too is considered to be excessive force.
他们想让我维护法律…
They want me to uphold the law...
…但他们捆住我的手脚
...but they tie my hands.
幸运的是…
Fortunately...
…我一直有它 我的老伙计
...there's always Old Reliable.
为什么要阻碍成功?
Why mess with success?
哦 谢谢
Uh, thanks.
- 你见过拉萨了吗? - （俄语）没有
Have you seen Lassard?
我受够你们这群笨蛋了
l have had it with you losers.
我会抓住康那利 因为我会用脑
l will capture Konali because l use my head.
- 是的 没错 - 以为我们抓不到他吗?
TACKLEBERRY: Yeah, right. CALLAHAN: Think we can lose him?
对不起 你能帮我吗?
Excuse me. ls possible you help me?
当然 哦…
Sure. Uh... .
你们能不能先走? 我一会儿就赶上你们
Why don't you guys run along and l'll catch up with you later.
嗯哼 当然可以
Uh - huh. Sure.
卡特琳娜 我能为你做什么?
Katrina, how can l help you?
你有没有如此渴望过一件事情?
You ever want something so badly it hurts?
- 有过 - 无论你怎样等待…
- Yes. - And no matter how much you wait...
…盼望着等待着 你却得不到你所想要的
...and hope and wait more, you don't get what you want?
嗯 是的
Well, yeah.
我的建议是：不要放弃 尽管去争取
But my advice is don't give up. Just go for it.
- 我想… - 好姑娘 让你的心告诉你该怎样做
- l want    - Thattagirl. Follow your heart.
- 我想… - 说吧!
- l want    - Say it.
- 我想休假 - 什么?
- l want my vacation. - What's that?
我等了三年 三年! 然后你们这群美国人来了
l wait three years. Three years. Then you Americans come.
塔林斯基 他把我派给你们
Talinsky, he assign me to you.
- 嗯 - 现在我没法休假了
- Mm - hm. - Now l can't go.
我有个计划
l have plan.
康那斯 我不离开你…
Connors, l don't leave you...
…除非是没有人了
...without anyone.
过来 我给你们选择了合适的替代人选
Come. l select suitable replacement for you.
她是部门里最棒的
She's best in department.
噢 我相信
Yeah, l'm sure she is.
看 我所知道的一切就是拉萨在机场就不见了
Look, all l know is Lassard disappear at airport.
组织搜索 但要保密
Organize search, find Lassard, but keep quiet.
- 你们来这干这什么? - 只是随便看看
- What are you doing here? - Just browsing.
啊
Ah.
嘿 尤里 那个翻译卡特琳娜 她很好 非常棒
Hey, Yuri, that translator, Katrina? Very good. She's excellent.
我们的人都很棒
All our people are excellent.
比如说 艾琳娜·佩特罗夫斯卡娅
For instance, this is lrina Petrovskaya.
她是人类分析专家
She is expert in forensics.
她只需通过人的一根头发…
She can tell you everything about person...
…就能分析出他的一切情况
...just by looking at one hair from head.
哟!
Ow!
嗯 通过我的观察 我得出了这些结论：这个家伙非常挑食…
Hmm. My observations conclude this man is picky eater...
…有恐高症…
...afraid of heights...
- …现在还是个处男 - 什么?
- ...and still a virgin. CONNORS: What?
我一点也不挑食
l'm not a picky eater.
康那斯学员也是个人娄分析学家
Cadet Connors is also a forensics expert.
也许您能慷慨地与我们一道分享您宝贵的专业经验
Maybe you'd be so generous as to share with us your expertise.
- 哦 当然 - 这个样品一直让我们很困惑
- Uh, sure. - This one puzzles us.
我们在犯罪现场只采到了一枚指纹
We were able to remove only one fingerprint from scene of crime.
这是我们唯一的…
This is our only clue...
…能够证明罪犯的线索
...to identity of criminal.
好 没问题
Okey - dokey.
怪不得你们弄不明白玻璃已经全碎了
No wonder you're puzzled. This glass is all cracked.
够了!
Enough!
下个任务 切尔诺贝利
Next assignment, Chernobyl.
对不起 中尉…
Excuse me, lieutenant...
…您的指挥官说过您和您的人会帮助我们
...but the chief said you and your men would be available to us.
完全正确 卡拉汉上尉 我这有合适的人选
Absolutely, Captain Callahan, and l have just the men for you.
这些人也是警察?
These guys are cops?
你有没有觉得我们在这里不受欢迎?
You get the feeling that we're not wanted here?
我来告诉你们我们该做什么
l'll tell you what we need to do.
- 我们应该让康那利知道我们在这 - 在他的地盘上
- We need to let Konali know we're here. - On his turf.
- 打他的痛处 - 我喜欢
- Hit him where it hurts. TACKLEBERRY: l like that.
- 揍他的脸 - 踹他的屁股
- Get in his face. - Kick some butt.
最好带上卡特琳娜
Better get Katrina.
嘿 伙计 干得不错嘛!
Hey, bud. Nice work.
这些要是全被烧光的话可真可惜
lt would be a shame to see this all go up in smoke.
- 你什么意思? - 发生了意外事件
- How do you mean? - Accidents happen.
突发火灾 房梁倒塌 工人…
Fire breaks out, beam gives way, workers
滚开!
Get out.
告诉康那利我不会给他一分钱
Tell Konali l won't pay his extortion money.
嘿 哥们 拉萨指挥官向你致敬
Hey, buddy. Commandant Lassard sends his regards.
我真是难以形容…
l can't tell you how it makes me feel...
…你们全家对我真是太 太 太慷慨了
...to be received so very, very generously into your family.
（俄语）
噢
Oh.
我自己来干
l'll take matters into my own hands.
他在干什么?
What is he doing?
- 长官 午饭时间了 - 在卧室里等我
- Sir, would you like to have lunch? - Meet me in the bedroom.
在浴室里
ln the bathroom.
- 长官? 在那等我!
- Sir? BELL HOP: Meet me there!
在那等你! 在那等你!
Meet you there! Meet you there!
这下水道真臭!
This sewer stinks.
于是美国人没说再见就走了
So Americans leave without saying goodbye.
俄国人说了再见却不走
Russians say goodbye without leaving.
噢 让我来
Oh, allow me.
（俄语）
"牧场是我家"
呕!
Ooh!
汤都臭了
This went rancid.
我向你保证…
过了今天 康那利就会知道这些警察已经在这儿了
After today, Konali's gonna know this cop's in town.
这是典型的俄罗斯浴室
This is a typical Russian bathhouse.
这么说这就是康那利的桑拿室了?
Okay. So this is Konali's sauna.
这只是前台 人们把偷来的珠宝拿到这里进行交易
lt's just a front. People come here to fence stolen jewels.
好吧 我们去脱衣服吧
All right. Let's get naked.
来吧 快点
Come on. Come on.
姑娘们 你们好啊
Hello, ladies.
嗨
Hi.
不错的浴室
Nice place you got here.
不许动!
Freeze!
你们继续吧…
You may resume...
…无论做什么
...whatever it is you were doing.
好了好了 我现在应该在康那利酒店的下面
Okay, okay. l should be right under Konali's restaurant.
- 喜欢那条项链吗? - 噢 当然 我亲爱的
- Did you like the necklace? WOMAN: Oh, yes, my pushki.
- 有多喜欢? - 事实上 我现在只穿着它…
- How much? - In fact, it is all that I am wearing.
我决定从现在起…
I decided that from now on...
我只戴钻石 钻石 钻石
...I will only wear diamonds, diamonds and diamonds.
- 是的 - 真的?
- Yes. - Really?
- 我一会儿去见你 怎么样? - 噢 我盼望着
KONALl: l'm going to see you later, right? WOMAN: Oh, I hope so.
我会给你一个惊喜
l'm going to bring you big surprise.
- 啊? 是什么? - 一条大日本蛇怎么样?
- What? - How about Big Skippy?
- 我喜欢大的 - 还有小的
- I love Big Skippy. - And Little Skippy.
不 不要小的
No, not the little one.
- 他让我心烦 - 好吧 我一会儿再给你打电话
- He bothers me. - All right. l call you later.
嘿 让开 别挡道!
Hey, move it. Down in front.
康那利先生 坏消息
Mr. Konali, we've got bad news.
关于美国警察的
lt's American police.
他们又给我们捣乱了
They're messing with our operation again.
这是最后一次了! 听到了没有?
No more. You hear me?
从现在起 我要把拉萨还有他的队员们一起赶走!
As of this moment l am putting a contract out on Lassard and his team!
揍扁他们!
We squash them!
我的小鱼 游游·拉萨
My fish, Swimmy Lassard.
每天这个时候他都要吃东西
He eats at this time every day.
高尔基公园
这会很好玩 弗拉迪
This will be fun, Vlady.
嘿 小屁孩儿 没长眼啊!
Hey, you little punk, get lost!
嘿 滚开!
Hey, spread out!
- 你没事吧? - 嗯
- You okay? - Yeah.
听着 不要认为他们有好车骑就是好人
Listen, just because they're good on bikes doesn't make them nice guys.
噢 瞧瞧你 好了
Man, look at you. Come on.
这是给你的 孩子
This one's for you, kid.
瞧好了
Now, check this.
那 别打歪了
There. Don't miss.
起来 弗拉迪
Vlady, get up.
我恨透狗了 再让我见着它们我要把它们杀光光
l hate dogs. l'm gonna shoot every dog l ever see.
瞧瞧这是什么一根火柴上一条红线
What have we got here? A match with a red line through
我在这儿已经呆了30分钟了
l've been here for 30 minutes.
如果康那利在里面我们还会看见他吗?
Shouldn't we see if Konali's inside?
俄国人办事真讲原则
The Russian work ethic.
知道吗 卡特琳娜 你对工作太认真了
You know, Katrina, you take this job too seriously.
你应该学会放松一下自己
You have to learn to loosen up.
我想放松
l want to loosen up.
我已经计划休假 去海滨
Had vacation planned. Go to beach.
现在我却跟你坐在长凳上
Now l sit on bench here with you.
你肯定跟塔林斯基说了?
You sure you speak with Talinsky?
- （俄语）是的 塔林斯基 - 我不明白
- Da, Talinsky. - l not understand.
我不该还呆在这
l should not be here.
嗯 你知道 卡特琳娜 有时你必须面对无法预知的事情
Well, you know, Katrina, sometimes you have to expect the unexpected.
- 我知道你这种人 - 我这种人?
- l know your type. - My type?
你们只喜欢猎艳 喜欢追赶
You just like to hunt fox. You like the chase.
卡特琳娜 今晚跟我出去吧 就一次
Katrina, go out with me tonight. Just one date.
给我次机会
Give me a chance.
（俄语）好吧
我今晚跟你出去
l go out with you tonight.
太棒了!
Excellent.
女士们先生们…
Ladies and gentlemen.
（俄语）女士们先生们…
…我向你们隆重介绍…
l would like to introduce to you...
…著名的马戏世家 赞姆斯科夫一家!
...the world - famous circus family, Zemskova.
是赞姆斯科夫一家! 他们可棒了!
lt's the Zemskov family. They're great.
他们从事马戏表演已经100多年了!
They've been doing this act for over 1 00 years.
100多岁还这么敏捷
They look amazingly spry for their age.
赞姆斯科夫一家把马戏表演从…
The Zemskov family passed the act down...
…祖父传给父亲 再传给儿女
...from grandfather to father to son and daughter.
这成为传统 并对外保密
lt's tradition. Keep secrets in family.
哎唷!
Ooh.
也许他们该对这事保密
Maybe that's one they should keep a secret.
再来几个这样的 赞姆斯科夫一家就该绝了
One more of those, it could be the end of the Zemskov family.
现在伊万·赞姆斯科夫将表演高难度动作!
And now lvan Zemskovi will perform the impossible!
三个后空翻!
The triple Salto Mortale.
伊万·赞姆斯科夫!
lvan Zemskovi!
我明白了
l know.
- 明白什么? - 你说谎了
- Know what? - You lie.
你说要帮我休假的
You tell me you get me off case as translator.
- 什么? - 而你却这样对塔林斯基说…
- l'm sorry? - lnstead you tell Talinsky...
…说我是个好翻译也就是说
...l'm great translator. Translation:
我根本休不了假
No vacation for me.
所以…
So...
…今晚我要报复一下 （俄语）明白?
...tonight l get even. Da?
让我们掌声感谢赞姆斯科夫一家!
Let's hear it for the great artist family, Zemskov.
女士们先生们 伊果和安德柳莎!
Ladies and gentlemen, lgor and Andrusha.
不好意思 我要去一下厕所
Excuse me. l have to go to the little clowns' room.
抓住他!
Get him.
不不不! 我很想 但我不能…
No, no, no, no. No, no, l'd like to, but l
不! 不!
No, no.
5分钟后我就回来 真的 我发誓
l'll come back in five minutes. l will. l promise you.
这是什么? 我会受伤吗?
What is that? ls this gonna hurt?
我会晕的 啊! 喔!
lt's not even lubricated. Ah! Whoa!
你们这些小丑什么时候停下来啊?
Don't you clowns know when to stop?
好了 该开始了 别害怕 闭上眼睛
Let's do it. Don't be afraid. Close your eyes.
观众们 请安静!
Everybody, quiet!
啊? 好吧 听着 壮汉们 啊
Huh? All right, listen here, Bozo
别忘了 是你们请我们来帮忙的 小鬼
Don't forget, you're the one that called us for help, buster.
噢 对不起 小鬼 不是我打的电话
Well, excuse me, buster, but l didn't place the call.
地铁真 真棒 太棒了!
Great, great subway. Terrific.
我是说 纽约就是屎 这里才叫棒
l mean, New York is a shithouse, but this is great.
你现在有本事抓住康那利了吗?
Well, have you been able to capture Konali?
我们就差一点儿
We were this close.
（俄语）是! 是! 是!
只要按我说的做 再加上我的先进装备两天之内保准你抓住他
Listen to me and use my equipment, you can capture him in two days.
（俄语）不! 不! 不! 不! 不! 不!
Na, na, na, na, na, na.
Na, na, na, na, na, na?
不
Nah.
- 俄国菜怎么样? - 想喝罗宋汤? 走?
- What about this Russian food? - You want borscht? We stop.
我才不想喝什么罗宋汤
l don't want any borscht.
我们现在打平了 （俄语）是吧?
So now we're even. Da?
不 卡特琳娜 今晚上我真得很愉快
Katrina, no. l had a wonderful time.
不过被人扔得很可怕…
All right. l had an awful time and l almost hurled...
…但至少我能跟你在一起
...but at least l got to spend some time with you.
我也很开心
l had good time too.
我为我所做的向你道歉 我只是
l'm sorry for what l did. l just
我只是想把你留在身边
l just wanted to keep you around.
没关系
lt's okay.
你在想什么?
What are you thinking about?
俄语"吻我"怎么说?
What's Russian for ''kiss me''?
我小声告诉你
l whisper it.
这样的翻译很准
lt doesn't seem to lose anything in the translation.
你知道 康那利…
You know, Konali...
…做了很多坏事
...he's done many bad things.
但他把你带到了我身边
But he brought you here.
康那利晚上会在哪里?
Where does Konali hang out at night?
- 赌场 - 我突然有种想赌一把的冲动
- The casino. - Suddenly l feel the need to gamble.
停止下注了 停止下注了
No more bets, please. No more bets.
康那利先生 见到您真是高兴
Mr. Konali, always a pleasure to see you, sir.
雅克 请把康那利先生带到他的桌旁
Jacquot, would you show Mr. Konali to his table?
那就是他
That's him.
请下注吧
Place your bets.
- 愿您玩得开心 先生 - 万一他发现你是警察怎么办?
- Have a nice evening, sir. - What if he finds out you're cop?
噢 他会发现的 在我逮捕他的时候
Oh, he will, when l arrest him.
待者 来杯玛格丽塔
Bartender, margarita, please.
- 请吧 邦德先生 - 我想我还是要毕雷矿泉水吧 瓶装的
- There you go, Monsieur Bond. - How about a Perrier in a bottle?
"他怎能这样做?
"他为何这样做?
- 喔噢! - "他从未这样做过
Whoa.
"我是否伤心?
"我的双眼会告诉你
"这是命中注定
"如果他愿意"
啊…噢
不错吧 啊 康那利先生?
Not bad, huh, Mr. Konali?
我从没见过这样的小妖精
Never before have l seen such an apparition.
嘿 快起来吧
Let's get up.
啊 是
Right.
真有女人味
Such a vision of womanhood.
"曾几何时
"我是他的唯一
"但现在却如此孤独
"噢 宝贝儿
"我是否伤心?
"直到今天
"现在他已离去
"我是否伤心?
- "噢 是的" - 康那利先生 这是黛比
- Oh, yeah. - Mr. Konali, meet Debbie.
黛比 你的名字像首歌
Debbie. The name sings to me.
黛 比
Debbie
- 耶! - 啊!
- Yeah! - Ah.
我敢说她成功了 我马上回来
l'd say she's in. Be right back.
- 您能给我签个名吗? - 嘿 我们老板正忙着呢
- Could l get an autograph? - Hey, the boss is busy.
- 对不起 我只耽误几秒钟 - 我说了 老板正忙着
- Sorry. This'll only take a second. - l said, the boss is busy.
- 噢 上帝 - 我跟你说 我们为什么不…
- Oh, God. - l tell you what. Why don't we... .
…抛硬币赌一下呢? 如果我赢了…
Why don't we flip for it? lf l win...
…就给我签名
...l get the autograph.
如果你赢了 我马上就离开
lf you win, l go away.
准备好了? 下注吧!
Ready? Call it.
请您给费雷迪签个名
lf you could just make it out to Freddie.
嘿 孩子
Hey, kid.
- 有工作吗? - 没有 我只是来这钓鱼的
- You got a job? - No. l'm just here for the herring.
你可以跟着我干
You should come work for me.
像你这样的孩子很有前途
Kid like you can go far.
你是牙医吗?
Do you offer a dental plan?
我喜欢这个孩子!
l love this kid!
好 好 好
Well, well, well.
你们就玩你们的化装游戏吧…
You can all go and play your little undercover games...
…等时候一到 我就会抓住康那利
...and when the time is right, l will arrest Konali.
给你看些我的宝贝儿的照片
l want to show you picture of my baby.
啊哈
Uh - huh.
这天我把她买回了家
This is the day l brought her home.
嗯
Hmm.
- 这是她的10000英里纪念 - 噢!
KONALl: Here she is at 1 0,000 miles. CALLAHAN: Ooh.
这是她第一次修理之后
KONALl: And this is after her first tune - up.
嗯哼
Mm - hm.
车真不错
Nice car.
- 是你的还是租的? - 只要是我碰过的东西…
- Do you own or lease? - Everything l touch...
…都是我的
...l own.
你的钱肯定很多
You must have an awfully large payroll.
还算够
Enough about me.
告诉我…
Tell me...
…这是真发吗?
...is that your real hair?
我的一切…都是真的
Everything about me is real.
真的?
Really?
真的
Really.
我想知道你的一切 我为你着魔
l want to know all about you. l find you fascinating.
命运让我们相会在此
We have an appointment with destiny.
但不是今晚
But not tonight.
那在什么时候?
When?
明天
Tomorrow.
有咖啡还有蛋糕
Coffee and cake.
我派车去接你
l send my car for you.
真是好车
Nice car.
哟嗬! 拉萨指挥官!
Yoo - hoo! Commandant Lassard!
不管你在哪儿 出来 快出来吧!
Come out, come out, wherever you are!
- 嘿 给我支烟 - 瞧见康那利的新妞儿了吗?
MAN 1 : Give me a cigarette. MAN 2: Did you see Konali's girlfriend?
美国佬
MAN 1 : American - ski.
噢 领带不错
Oh, nice tie - ski.
嘿 给我来瓶伏特加
Okay, get me some vodka.
可恶!
Damn!
干嘛不试试"俄罗斯之爱"?
Why don't you try ''from Russia with love''?
"俄罗斯之爱"
''Russia with love. ''
- 你是谁? - 不关你事
CONNORS: Who are you? - None of your business.
- 你在这干什么? - 玩游戏
- What are you doing here? - Playing games.
嘿 停下!
Hey, knock it off.
Hey, cut it out.
我知道你要什么…
l know what you want...
…但你得不到
...but you can't have it.
- 你怎么了? - 你知道吗…
- What's wrong with you? - Did you know...
…我已经连着72小时没吃东西了
...that l have been in this room for 72 hours straight with no food?
这屋里只有我…
Just me...
…和这只小熊
...and the bear.
没吃东西?
No food?
没吃
No.
那兹饼干怎么样?
Nuts?
- 你的小游戏结束了 - 不 还没有!
- Your little game is over. - No, not yet.
明天一切都会结束…
Tomorrow it'll all be over...
…康那利就能控制全世界!
...and Konali will have the power.
现在能让我起来了吗?
Could you let me up now, please?
我的期限已经快到了
l'm on kind of a deadline.
只要康那利说句话…
And with Konali...
…我的期限就到了
...he takes ''deadline'' literally.
我要让全世界的人见识一下…
l'm about to show the world something bigger...
…他们从未见过的伟大的事情
...than they have ever seen in their puny existence.
但是…
But...
…我想先让你知道
...l want to show you my thing first.
是不是能在我脖子上绕圈的东西?
ls it something l could wrap around my neck?
你很激动
You're warm.
是能让我玩的东西?
ls it something l could play with?
- 你有点着急了 - 噢 我快受不了了 康尼
- You're getting warmer. - Oh, the suspense is killing me, Koni.
- 告诉我吧 - 是个游戏!
- Tell me what it is. - lt's a game!
但不是一般的游戏
But not just any game.
是旧游戏的新版本
New version of old game...
- 我会赢得一切… - 噢!
- ...where l become big winner... - Oh.
- 通过一把神秘钥匙的帮助 - 神秘钥匙?
- ...with the help of a secret key. - Secret key?
钥匙?
Key?
- 你在干嘛? - 哦…
- What are you doing? - Uh... .
没什么
Nothing.
老板要从这间屋里拿他的电脑钥匙
Boss wants his computer key from his office.
不在这 在他的另一间办公室里…
lt's not here. lt's at his other office...
…在酒店里
...in the restaurant.
再见
Bye.
喔啊!
Whoa!
是激光报警器 我们只要一踏上地板…
That's a laser grid. We set one foot on that floor...
…就会触动这里所有的警报
...and every alarm in this place goes off.
我们必须想办法到达开关那里
We've got to get to that cutoff switch over there.
嘿 塔克 我找到了
Hey, Tack, l got it.
好 靠后站 只有这样才能把保险箱弄开
Okay, stand back. There's only one way to get this safe open.
等一下 你把这玩意儿炸开 康那利就知道我们在这儿了
Wait a minute. You blow that thing, Konali's gonna know we were here.
嗯 那我们怎么办?
Hmm. What are we gonna do?
你可真神奇
You're amazing.
这没什么钥匙
There's no key in here.
钥匙!
Keys!
- 快走 你个小骗子 - 别伤害我 好吗?
- Move, you little weasel. - Don't hurt me, okay
- 嘿! - 亚当
- Hey! - Adam.
- 游戏带来了吗? - 当然
- You have game? - Sure.
我超越了我自己 这个游戏…
l surpassed myself. This game...
…比以往的任何游戏都要伟大
...will be even bigger than the last one.
世界是我的了!
The world is mine.
去复制几份 我们要测试一下
Go run off a dozen copies. We have to test it.
把它们送给我们的几个游戏迷：
Send it to some of our more dedicated game players:
总统 市长…
The president, the mayor...
…拉科夫局长
...Chief of Police Rakov.
我现在能得到酬金了吗?
Can l get paid now?
噢
Oh.
在邮包里
lt's in the mail.
你也是
And so are you.
噢 不 又来了
Oh, no. Not again.
还有…
So...
- …你们有没有抓住拉萨的队员? - 没有
- ...did you get any of Lassard's team? - No.
但你们确实白领拉萨了 是吗?
But you did get Lassard, yes?
没有
No.
你们这群废物!
You bumbling nincompoops!
你们还配叫自己男人?
You call yourselves men?!
我们肯定能找人帮忙
There must be someone we can call.
嗯 我们还没找过警察
We haven't called the police.
"致美国警察们：
''To American police - ski:
"今晚 波尔绍剧院…
Bolshoi Theatre, tonight.
"…康那利进行偷来的武器交易
Konali to buy stolen shipment of weapons.
"你们一定要制止他
You must stop him.
"一位朋友"
A friend. ''
你知道我不懂俄语
You know l don't speak Russian.
但是 亲爱的 这只是场芭蕾
But, sweetheart, it's a ballet.
嘿 谁要榛果 新鲜的榛果! 接着!
Hey, who wants some nuts?! l got fresh nuts over here. Catch.
给你 先生! 噢 不 你那太远 够不着
There you go, mister. No, it didn't reach you long enough.
二层的 接着!
Up, topside!
哈 班尼先生 给你!
l gotcha! There you go, Mr. Benny!
- 啊! - 对不起 女士!
Ah! Sorry, lady.
谁还要? 这还有!
Who wants nuts? Right over here!
让开 老女人 噢 对不起 请原谅 夫人
Excuse me, babushka. l'm sorry. Excuse me, ma'am.
- 您的票 先生 - 我没票
- Ticket, please. - l don't have a ticket.
- 您需要买张票 - 我是个美国警察…
- You need a ticket. - l'm an American police captain...
…正在执行公务 我不需要什么票
...on assignment. l don't need a ticket.
- 很抱歉 您必须得买票 - 你难道还不明白?
- l'm sorry. You must have ticket. - Don't you understand?
我要进去逮捕罪犯
l have to arrest somebody in there.
没有票您不能进去逮捕罪犯
You cannot arrest anyone without a ticket.
你这样想? 好吧 我们走着瞧
You think so? Well, we'll just see about that.
对不起 让开 让开
Excuse me. Make way. Make way.
肯定是个替补
Must be a replacement.
- 哈里斯上尉 快走开! - 塔克贝利!
Captain Harris! Get out of here. HARRlS: Tackleberry!
- 快! - 你在这干什么?
- Now! HARRlS: What are you doing here?
我们该下去!
We've got to get off!
快!
Go!
噢!
Oh!
- 塔克贝利 康那利! - 这边!
- Tackleberry! Konali! - Over here.
- 起开! - 我们应该离开这!
DANCER: Go away! - We gotta get out of here!
是康那利!
lt's Konali!
快点 别让他看见我们! 快!
Come on, before he sees us! Come on!
我看见康那利了! 康那利! 我看见康那利了!
l saw Konali. Konali! l saw Konali!
- 那是康那利! 把我放下来! - 我知道 长官 我知道!
- That's Konali! Put me down! - l know, sir! l know, sir!
- 康那利! - 我知道!
- Konali! - l know!
不许动!
Freeze!
你被捕了!
You're under arrest.
- 你们在干什么? - 逮捕你
What are you doing? - Arresting you.
他是我的! 我要抓住他!
His butt is mine! l'll arrest him!
因为你卖给罪犯武器
For selling weapons to a known criminal.
"阳光孩子"
''Sunshine Kids. ''
我们中计了
We've been set up.
我对你们感到非常厌恶
l am completely disgusted with you all.
我很高兴我的好朋友拉萨不知道这事
l am glad my good friend, Commandant Lassard, knew nothing about this.
你们让你们的制服受辱…
You are a disgrace to your uniforms...
…也让我尴尬无比
...and an embarrassment to me.
尤里 你知道该怎么办 去吧
Yuri, you know what to do. Do it.
从他从莫斯科回来…
Ever since he return from Moscow...
…我就一直努力想把康那利抓住 哪怕流血牺牲!
...l have been trying to capture Konali red - handed!
但现在你们这群跳华尔兹的牛仔把我的工作击了个粉碎!
And now you cowboys waltz in and smash my work to pieces!
现在 要是我的人稍微瞧康那利一眼…
So now, if my police look at Konali wrong...
…他都会叫唤这是骚扰!
...Konali will scream harassment!
美国人…
Americans...
…你们因此被命令离开俄国
...you are hereby ordered to leave Russia.
懂了吗?
You understand?
出去!
Get out!
在明早3点以前!
By 3:00 tomorrow!
你也是!
Or else!
还有你…
And as for you... .
长官? 提醒您一下飞机3点起飞
Sir? Wanna remind you the plane leaves at 3:00.
在浴室里!
ln the bathroom.
长官?
Sir?
这个牌子让我觉得有点不对劲
Something about that sign disturbs me.
妈妈
Mama.
- 你想我们应该 ? - 我在你前面
- What do you say we   ? - l'm way ahead of you.
长官?
Sir?
在浴室里!
（俄语）不 不 不!
另一个包 另一个大包! 大包! 把它给我! 噢喔!
The other bag. The other   Big bag - ski, big bag. Here, give it to me. Ow!
琼斯! 把我扶起来!
Jones! Get me up!
我从未受过这样的奇耻大辱!
l have never been humiliated like this before!
- 那你受过其它样的奇耻大辱? - 闭嘴吧 琼斯 闭嘴!
- So you've been humiliated other ways? - Just shut up, Jones.
- 噢 是 长官 - 康那斯!
- Oh, yes, sir. - Connors!
我还以为你不来了呢
l thought you weren't coming.
我不想让我的心碎了现在一切都太晚了
Didn't want my heart to be broken. Now it's too late.
卡拉汉! 他们抓走了卡拉汉!
Callahan! They got Callahan!
- 怎么回事? - 卡拉汉!
CALLAHAN: Who the hell? - Callahan!
- 康那斯! - 快追!
- Connors! HARRlS: Let's go!
别管我! 小心你自己!
Don't worry about me! Take care of yourself!
快 快 快 快 快!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
停 停 停 停 停!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
快! 上来! 快 快 快! 走! 快开车! 快!
Come on! Move - ski, move - ski, move - ski! Go! Go! Start it up! Go!
康那斯! 坚持住! 康那斯!
Connors! Hang on, Connors!
闭嘴!
Shut up.
军士 你就不能开快点? 让这玩意儿开快点!
Sergeant, can't you go any faster? Make this thing go!
- 他会死的! - 不 不! 我的队员是不会死的…
KATRlNA: He's going to get killed! - Nobody on my team gets killed...
- …这是命令! - 我会死的!
- ...and that's an order! CONNORS: l'm gonna get killed!
呀!
Jeez!
把他甩下去!
Shake him off!
喔!
Whoa!
- 塔克贝利 把你的枪给我! - 是 长官!
- Tackleberry, give me your gun. - Yes, sir!
这是颗跟踪子弹 只要把它打到车上 我们就能一直跟着它!
This is a locator bullet. lf we can hit the car with it, we can follow it anywhere.
是 长官!
Yes, sir!
（俄语）好吧 瞧好吧
Sasha, just get me one clean shot.
开枪 塔克! 开枪! 快!
Fire it, Tack. Fire it, let's go!
塔克贝利 干漂亮点! 打中那辆车!
Tackleberry, do something right for a change. Hit that car!
打中啦!
Gotcha.
（俄语）嘿 同志 美国警察!
- 哥们 帮帮忙! - 俄国人!
- My buddy! Help! HARRlS: Russkies!
俄国人 俄国人 上摩托车!
Russkies, in the motorcycle!
快 快 快 快 快 快 快!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
你听不懂英语吗? 再快点!
Don't you understand English? Faster!
这是干什么? 牛仔竞技吗? 快!
What is this, a rodeo? Come on!
开近点!
Get closer!
康那斯!
Connors!
康那斯! 因为我的计划你该庆幸你还活着!
Connors! You better be glad you weren't killed, because l've got a plan.
快点 上车! 快! 快!
Hurry up. Move it, move it, move it!
它起效了
lt works.
康那利的别墅
真丢人! 在我的人面前! 在同族面前!
Shamed. ln front of my men! My peers!
- 还有我的妈妈! - 真对不起!
- My mommy! - Sorry about that.
你! 你要为你所做的付出代价!
You. You will pay dearly for what you have done!
我知道
l know.
- 你得嫁给我! - 哇喔!
- You will marry me. - Wow.
- 多漂亮的衣服 - 谢谢
- Nice getup. - Thanks.
- 我们可以分享一切 - 好的
- We're going to share everything. - Okay.
正中要害!
Right in bull's - eye!
我不能相信你的固执! 你本可以拥有一切的!
l cannot believe your obstinacy! You could have had it all!
而你却背着我! 我要埋了你!
lnstead you betray me? l am going to bury you!
- 噢! - 什么? 什么? 我忙着呢!
- Ooh! - What? What? l'm busy!
游戏已经进入警局的电脑!
The game is in the police station computer.
进去了 耶!
l'm in! Yes!
现在输入密码 你转过去!
Now for the key. My secret code. Turn around.
3 4 5 哈!
- Three, four, five. KONALl: Yes.
商店那准备好了? 我得走了 小蛋糕
Everything ready at the warehouse? Got to go, cupcake.
一会儿再跟人联系 看看你是否回心转意
l get in touch with you later. See if you change your mind.
（俄语）再见!
啊!
Ah!
打倒你了!
Shoot him.
瞧啊 他给我们留了个妞儿
Look, he left us play toy.
我很需要这样
l really need this.
塔克贝利 从左面窗户进去
Tackleberry, crash the left window.
琼斯 康那斯 卡特琳娜 从右边
Jones, Connors, Katrina, the right window.
我跟这些家伙从房顶上进去
l'll go through the roof with the guys.
- 从门进怎么样? - 行了 走吧 走吧 走!
- How about the door? - Well, move it, move it, move it.
尝尝这个 你个变态!
Take that, perverts!
应该是旁边这屋 数到三我们冲进去!
This next room has to be it. Crash through on the count of three.
- 1 2 - 不许动!
- One, two    - Freeze!
- 你们听见我喊三了吗? - 我已经控制这里了
- Did anyone hear me say ''three''? - l took care of it.
- 他在哪? - 他走了
- Where is he? - He's gone.
康那利已经从这房子里逃走了
Konali has left the building.
他得到了某种程序 使得他能进入警局的计算机系统
Some command let him break into the police computer system.
- 如果他真进去了 我们就没办法制止他了 - 康那利的黑客在他的游戏上做了手脚
- lf he gets in, we can't stop him. - His hacker was working on the game.
- 这就是那把神秘的钥匙 - 他们正用船出一批货
- The key must be on it. CALLAHAN: They're sending a shipment.
- 他们在他的商店 - 走!
- They're at the warehouse. - Let's go.
等会儿 塔林斯基说如果你们三点还不走就会缉捕你们
Wait. Talinsky said if you're not on the 3:00 flight he'll arrest you.
她说的对 我们快走
She's right. Let's go anyway.
- 没问题 - 在那! 是他们! 快 快 快!
JONES: No problem. - There, that's them! Go, go, go!
- 是塔林斯基 - 行了 这下有麻烦了
CALLAHAN: lt's Talinsky. - Okay, it's a problem.
（俄语）
好 很好
Good. Good.
48小时后 全世界的商店里都会有"新游戏"销售
ln 48 hours, ''The New Game'' will be in stores worldwide.
我们怎么停车?
How we gonna park?
（俄语）天哪!
Sasha!
走! 我们走! 快! 快! 快!
Let's go! Let's go! Move it! Move it! Move it!
好了 听着! 听着! 琼斯 把手铐给我
All right, listen up! Listen up! Jones, give me those handcuffs.
- 现在 记住 我来抓拿康那利 - 快开 快开 快开!
- Now, remember: l will arrest Konali. - Come on. Come on. Come on.
现在 我数到三 然后进攻1 2
Now, we attack on three. One, two
停 停 停!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
广告将持续不断地播出三个月
Advertising spots will run consecutive days for the next three months.
还有电视台想请您坐客《早安莫斯科》
And A.M. Moscow wants you for a guest spot.
别让车熄火!
Keep car running!
- 母盘和密码在哪? - 正如您要求…
- Where is master disk and passkey? - lt's back inside your safe.
…在您酒店保险箱的最里面
ln the restaurant office, as you requested.
很好
Good.
嘿 娜塔莎!
Hey, Natasha.
- 我要是还需要什么我会告诉你的 - 你需要找个好律师
- l'll let you know if l need anything else. CONNORS: You need a good attorney.
康斯坦丁·康那利 我以法律的名义逮捕你
Konstantine Konali, l arrest you in the name of the law.
住手! 你们都住手!
Stop. Everybody stop.
- 把枪抬起来! - 我已经把康那利抓住了 他是我的囚犯
- Put up gun! - l have arrested Konali. He's my prisoner.
你们别再做在波尔绍剧院那些让我蒙羞的事了!
l will not be humiliated again like Bolshoi disaster.
我已经见过这个
l've seen this before.
我在拉科夫的办公室里玩过这个
l was playing with this in Rakov's office.
我的律师会对你们这些恶意行为进行起诉…
My lawyer's going to sue for malicious prosecution...
…你们对我进行国际性的骚扰 严重伤害了我的感情
...intentional harassment and breaking a guy's heart.
你起诉不了谁的 因为我会把你送进监狱
You're not going to sue anybody, because l am sending you to jail.
- 你们有证据吗? - 证据? 证据?
- Do you have proof? - Proof? Proof.
- 我们有证据吗? - 有
- Do we have proof? CALLAHAN: Yes.
中尉 就在你鼻子下面
Lieutenant, it's right under your nose.
警局电脑的号码是多少?
What's the number of the police computer?
291 3855
291 3855.
- 那是机密 - 输入"康那利"
- That's top security    - Type in ''Konali. ''
- 快点 康那斯 再试试 - 试试"康斯坦丁"
JONES: Come on, Connors. Keep trying. - Try ''Konstantine. ''
- 不行 - 等一下 我记的是五个字母
- No. - Wait. lt was five letters.
我看见康那利敲了五下键盘
l saw Konali type five letters.
"贪婪"
''Greed. ''
输入"贪婪"
Type in ''greed. ''
机密信息!
Classified information!
康那利在他的电脑游戏里加入了一个程序
Konali hid a program in his computer game.
他能人不知鬼不晓地得到用户的文件
Nobody would know it was there. lt allowed him access to the user's files.
就像从小孩嘴里抢糖果一样简单
lt's like stealing candy from a baby.
也能得到政府的高级机密文件
Or top - secret information from a government.
我终于抓住你了 康那利 哈!
l finally got you, Konali. Ha!
哈里斯上尉?
Captain Harris?
啊!
噢 不
Oh, no.
为我的俄罗斯家庭干杯!
A toast to my new Russian family.
（俄语）
不好意思 我要去一下洗手间
Excuse me. l have to go to the boys' room.
噢 对不起
Oh, excuse me.
- 我还以为这里是洗手间 - 你!
- l thought this was the bathroom. - You!
- 拉萨! - 啊 是的!
- Lassard. - Why, yes.
您认识我真让我感到无比荣耀我不知道我们在哪
l'm flattered you recognize me. l'm not sure where
- 你抓不到我! - 我不想抓你
- You can't have me! - l don't want you.
- （法语）防卫吧! - 防什么?
- En garde! - On what?
有什么临终请求吗?
You have any last requests?
上帝! 上帝! 我的脚!
God! God! Sonny Bono!
起来 乖宝宝!
LASSARD: Upsy - daisy!
啊哈!
Ah - ha!
- 你看上去挺眼熟 - 别跟我耍花样 拉萨!
- You look familiar. - Don't play with me, Lassard.
- 是在巴黎吗? - 不 不在那
- Was it Paris? - No, not Paris.
- 罗马? - 不是
- Rome? - Not Rome.
你以为你能把我当傻子耍吗?
You think you can play me the fool?
你永远也抓不到我 拉萨!
You'll never take me, Lassard!
抓不到康斯坦丁·康那利!
Not Konstantine Konali!
啊! 我想起你了!
Ah! l remember you now.
你因反俄国 反美国…
You're under arrest for crimes against Russia...
…及人民罪被捕! 哈!
...and America and their citizens! Ha!
噢! 真棒!
Do it!
- 今天… - 今天 今天
- Today... - Today, today.
- …我们向…. - 我们向 我们向
- ...we have shown... JONES: We have shown, we have shown.
嗯
Hm.
- …全世界的人民… - 全世界的人民
- ...people everywhere... - People everywhere
…表明美俄两国亲如兄弟
...that Americans and Russians are brothers.
我向您还有您的队员致敬!
l honor you and your team.
请拉萨指挥官到台前来
Would Commandant Lassard please join me at podium?
同志!
Comrade.
现在 向我的美国朋友送上特殊的礼物…
And now, as a special tribute to our American friends...
…向你们致敬!
...l salute you all.